https://www.virginaustralia.com/au/en/\_cookiesAcceptance/

disabled Mode

    Book now

    Flight specials

    Manage booking

    Business Class flights
    
    Domestic flights

    International flights

    Our network

    Popular domestic routes

    Popular international routes

    Flying with us

    Specific travel

    Baggage

    Airport information

    Onboard experience

    International travel

    Virgin Australia Business Flyer

    Corporate travel
    
    * Why choose Virgin Australia

    The basics

    Partners and offers

    Shopping online

    Flying and status

Privacy policy
==============

Policies
--------

Protecting Your privacy
-----------------------

Virgin Australia is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This commitment is demonstrated in our Privacy Policies which tell you how we manage your personal information and how to contact us if you have any privacy concerns. 

If our Privacy Policies do not answer a question that you have about how we manage your personal information, please [call or email us](https://www.virginaustralia.com/au/en/help/contact-us/).

* Read the [Virgin Australia Privacy Policy](https://www.virginaustralia.com/au/en/about-us/policies/privacy/privacy-policy/) 
* Read the [Velocity Frequent Flyer Privacy Policy](https://www.velocityfrequentflyer.com/content/Privacy/privacy-policy/ "Link opens an external site which may or may not meet accessibility guidelines.")

For specific information on the types of information that we collect about you and why we do this, you should read the appropriate privacy statement:

* [Privacy Statement for Virgin Australia Business Flyer and Loyalty](https://www.virginaustralia.com/au/en/about-us/policies/privacy/privacy-statement-business-flyer/ "privacy-statement-business-flyer")

Contact us
----------

If you have a concern about your privacy or wish to make a privacy complaint, you can contact us by:

1. [Calling us](https://www.virginaustralia.com/au/en/help/contact-us/)
2. Writing to us at the below address: 

**Privacy Officer  
**Legal department  
PO Box 1034  
Spring Hill QLD 4004  
  
Email: [privacy@virginaustralia.com](mailto:privacy@virginaustralia.com)

Our Privacy policies contain details about our complaint handling process and what to do if you are not satisfied with our response.

* #### Support
    
* #### Get to know us
    
* #### Other services
    
* #### Download our app

In the spirit of reconciliation Virgin Australia acknowledges the traditional custodians of country throughout Australia and their connections to land, sea, sky and community. We pay our respect to their Elders past and present and extend that respect to all Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples today.

* © Virgin Australia Airlines Pty Ltd ABN 36 090 670 965
